

Contact Me

bojana.trajkovska1@yahoo.com +38978503591 www.linkedin.com/in/trajkovskabojana/ www.behance.net/bojanatrajkov1

Skills

- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- UI/UX Design
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD
- SQL
- WordPress
- · Quality Assurance Engineering
- · Microsoft Office

Publications

- Measuring visual attention using an eyetracking biosensor (Master's thesis)
- Artificial intelligence (Graduate thesis)

Courses

- UI/UX Design
- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Adobe Photoshop
- Graphic Design
- C++

Languages

- English (Full professional proficiency)
- French (Professional working proficiency)

Projects

- Digital Marketing Strategy: Victoria's Secret
- · Website: Authors & Employees
- Website: Classy Coffee
- · Website: Judicial expertise
- Case Study: Mobile restaurant app
- · Mobile App: Meditation
- Mobile App: Book depository
- Mobile App: Food delivery
- Landing page: Vacation rental
- Webpage: Color theory
- Webpage: Portfolio
- · Webpage: Movies

Bojana Trajkovska

UI/UX Designer

MSc in Computer Software Technology Engineering Frontend Developer & Web Designer at Blasoft Solutions, Sales & Marketing Specialist at Maltini Travel Agency and Branch Manager & Customer Service Specialist at Euroins Insurance Company

About

Experienced UI/UX Designer, Frontend Developer & Web Designer, Sales & Marketing Specialist and Branch Manager & Customer Service Specialist skilled in: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, WordPress, SQL and Microsoft Office. Strong engineering professional with a Master's degree focused in Computer Software Technology Engineering from International Slavic University.

Work Experience



Branch Manager & Customer Service Specialist

Euroins Insurance Company Mar 2022 - Present



Sales and Marketing Specialist & Shore Excursion Staff

Maltini Travel Agency Mar 2022 - Present



Frontend Developer & Web Designer

Blasoft Solutions Sep 2021 - Nov 2021 (3 months)



Shop Assistant

SEA LIFE CENTRE (BLACKPOOL) May 2019 - Oct 2019 (6 months) Blackpool, England, United Kingdom



Lifeguard

Dutch Springs
Jun 2018 - Sep 2018 (4 months)
Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, United States

Education



Quality Assurance Engineering

Institution: Seavus Education and Development Center Manual and Automation Testing



Master of Computer Software Technology Engineering Faculty of informatics

Institution: International Slavic University



Web Design

Grade: 9.14

Institution: Seavus Education and Development Center HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, PHP, UI/UX, Adobe XD, MySQL, WordPress, SEO, Digital Marketing



Frontend Development Academy

Institution: SkillUp Academy